Turkus, Burton B. Arbitration Files 5712
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Port Authority of New York and New Jersey vs. Port Authority Police Benevolent Association, Inc., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  9/15/78. Issue: Rates of pay - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Port Authority of New York and New Jersey vs. Port Authority Police Benevolent Association, Inc, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  9/28/77. Issue: Rates of pay - holidays. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Port Authority of New York and New Jersey vs. Port Authority Police Benevolent Association, Inc., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  11/5/76. Issue: cancelled.
- Pot Levin Machine Company vs. UAW, Local 365., 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  5/18/81. Issue: cancelled.
- Pratt and Whitney Aircraft vs. UAW, Local 1234, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11a)
  6/26/70. Issue: Insubordination - misconduct. Includes: Award only.
- Prudential Lines, Inc. vs. Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  2/2/77. Includes: No Award.
- Prudential Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  8/14/79. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Prudential Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  9/2/80. Issue: cancelled.
- Prudential Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  11/18/80. Issue: Fringe Benefits - Employer contributions. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, System Council U-2, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  11/22/76. Issue: Rates of pay - layoff. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  2/24/76. Issue: Severance pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, System Council, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  11/5/76. Issue: Bargaining unit - assignment of work outside unit. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, System Council, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  6/24/76. Issue: Assignment of jobs. Includes: Briefs, correspondence, exhibits.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, Local 2060, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  12/21/76. Issue: Discipline - suspension - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, System Council U-2, Local 2178, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  7/22/75. Issue: Management rights - consolidation of departments. Includes: Award only.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  6/6/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work. Includes: Award only.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. IBEW, System Council, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  3/1/71. Issue: Promotion. Includes: Award only.
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  6/6/77. Issue: Discipline - suspension - absences - tardiness. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Puerto Rico Marine Management, Inc, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Includes: Exhibits. No Award
- Puerto Rico International Airways vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  6/30/77. Issue: withdrawn.
- R.K. Baking Corporation vs. Baking and Confectionery Workers International, Local 3., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  12/19/73. Issue: Rates of pay - holidays. Includes: Award only.
- Radio City Music Hall vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  11/13/80. Issue: settled. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, briefs, correspondence, exhibits.
- Raver Films, Inc. vs. United Scenic Artists, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  4/19/76. Issue: Rates of pay - termination of business. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Raytheon Company vs. IBEW, Local 1505, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  12/6/77. Issue: Suspension - back pay awards - pending court action. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents.
- Reeves-Teletype Corporation vs. NABET, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  6/22/77. Issue: withdrawn.
- Refined Syrups and Sugars, Inc. vs. ILA, Local 1814, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  1/12/79. Issue: Bidding - downward or lateral bids. Issue: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Restaurant Associates, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 131, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9a)
  1/29/73. Issue: Discipline - discharge - violation of company rules. Includes: Award only.
- Restaurant Associates Industries vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  5/3/82. Includes: Correspondence, briefs. No Award.
- Restaurant Associates Industries vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 76, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  1/22/76. Issue: cancelled.
- Revere Sugar Corporation vs. ILA, Local 1814, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  2/19/80. Issue: Workweek - past practice - management rights. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Revere Smelting and Refining Corporation vs. National Organization of Industrial Trade Union, United Trades Local 1, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  11/9/76. Issue: Termination - rates of pay - vacation pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, legal documents, exhibits.
- Rheem Manufacturing Company vs. USA, Local 3966, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  1/8/79. Issue: withdrawn.
- RKO General, Inc. vs. IATSE, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  5/24/76. Issue: Layoff. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits. No Award.
- Roadway Express, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 707, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  5/17/77. Issue: withdrawn
- Russian Tea Room vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  Not dated. Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Russian Tea Room vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  11/20/79. Issue: withdrawn.
- Ryetown Hilton vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  11/1/82. Includes: No Award.
- Ryetown Hilton vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  Not dated. Issue: withdrawn.
- Safety Electrical Equipment Corporation vs. United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 296, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  10/22/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercation. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- St. Barnabas Hospital vs. Union of Security Personnel of Hospitals and Health Related Facilities, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  4/22/80. Issue: withdrawn
- St. Lukes Hospital Center vs. NYSNA, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  1/30/81. Issue: Benefit funds - contributions. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- St. Mary's Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  10/22/81. Includes: No Award
- St. Mary's Hospital vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  1/8/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft - improper job attitude. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- St. Petersburg Limousine Service, Inc. vs. BRAC, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  10/5/76. Issue: Bidding and posting - hiring of part-time employees. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- St. Petersburg Limousine Service, Inc. vs. BRAC, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  5/10/77. Issue: Welfare fund - contributions. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Saturday Review, Inc. vs. American Newspaper Guild, Local 3, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  11/19/62. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -neglect of duty. Includes: Award only.
- Schaefer Brewing Company vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  7/21/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -customer relations - neglect of duty. Includes: Award only.
- Schaefer Brewing Company vs. IBT, Local 46, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  7/9/69. Issue: Management rights. Includes: Award only.
- SCM Corporation vs. IAM, District 15, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  2/3/76. Issue: Layoff - rates of pay - notice. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Scovill Manufacturing Company vs. UAW, Local 1604, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  6/14/74. Issue: withdrawn.
- SDS Distributing Corporation vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  1/23/78. Issue: Rates of pay, lower classification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- SDS Distributing Corporation vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  6/27/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Seaboard World Airlines, Inc. vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 504, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  11/14/77. Issue: Insurance - Workmen's Compensation - disability benefits. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Sea-Land Service, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  6/27/63. Issue: Layoff - severance pay. Includes: Award only.
- Sea-Land Service, Inc. vs. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  12/16/80. Issue: Discriminatory supervision. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Sealtest Foods vs. IBT, Local 338, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  3/12/73. Issue: Bargaining unit work. Includes: Award only.
- Sexton and Company vs. IBT, Local 202, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  1/20/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- SGS Control Services, Inc. vs. ILA, Local 1655, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  6/13/80. Issue: Bargaining unit - rates of pay - fringe benefits. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits
- Shell Company (Puerto Rico) Ltd. vs. IAM, Lodge 2201, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  2/24/76. Issue: Scheduling - work shift. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Sikorsky Aircraft vs. IBT, Local 1150, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  4/23/81. Issue: Demotion - absences. Includes: Transcripts, legal documents, exhibits, correspondence.
- Sikorsky Aircraft vs. IBT, Local 1150, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  10/29/82. Issue: Promotion. Includes: Transcripts, correspondence, exhibits, Arbitrator's notes.
- Simco Stores, Inc. vs. RWDSU, Local 287, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  3/19/70. Issue: withdrawn.
- Simco Stores, Inc. vs. RWDSU, Local 287, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  8/24/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - termination - severance pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Simco Stores, Inc. vs. RWDSU, Local 287, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  2/9/79. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Sloan, Inc. vs. RWDSU, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  7/10/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - call-in - alcoholism. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, legal documents, exhibits.
- Sophia Berzamanis vs. Ice Cream Industry Drivers and Ice Cream Employees Union, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  11/7/77. Issue: Disability - benefits - pension plan. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Southern Airways, Inc. vs. Flight Attendants in the Service of Southern Airways, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, transcripts, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Southern Airways, Inc. vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Local 553, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  10/2/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Improper personal conduct - dishonesty. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Southern Airways, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  9/20/76. Issue: Termination - qualifications. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Southern Florida Hotel and Motel Association vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees, Local 355, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  4/9/75. Issue: Suspension - insubordination. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Southern Florida Hotel and Motel Association vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-Rise Employees, Local 355 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Not dated. Issue: Contract extension. Includes: No Award.
- Southampton Construction Corporation vs. Joint Board, Culinary Employees, Local 1115., 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  3/10/77. Issue: Certification election. Issue: Correspondence, briefs.
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  7/11/79. Issue: Leaves of Absence - maternity leave. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  10/20/82. Issue: Discharge. Includes: No Award.
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  5/17/76. Issue: Rates of pay - holiday pay. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  5/23/1977
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  6/29/70. Issue: Discipline - discharge - fights and altercation. Includes: Award only.
- Steinway and Sons vs. United Furniture Workers of America, United Piano Workers Union, Local 102, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  12/28/77. Issue: withdrawn
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 1, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  8/30/78. Issue: Vacation pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits. No Award.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  7/19/82. Issue: Layoff. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, exhibits. No Award.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  3/7/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper job attitude -general attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  6/8/78. Issue: Scheduling - holiday pay. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  9/3/76. Issue: Certification election
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  3/25/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - plant rules. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  5/12/82. Issue: cancelled
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  7/3/81. Issue: Certification election.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 267, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  11/6/78. Issue: Holiday pay - scheduling. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 6, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  3/31/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - misconduct. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  8/6/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - disloyalty. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  6/17/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 69, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  7/29/77. Issue: withdrawn.
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 15, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  6/21/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, legal documents
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 267, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  11/30/76. Issue: Dishonesty - theft. Includes: Award only
- Stevens, H.M., Inc. vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 54, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  4/16/75. Issue: Strikes. Includes: Award only
- Strick Corporation vs. IBT, Local 816, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  11/15/78. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Strick Corporation vs. IBT, Local 816, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  1/21/81. Issue: Rates of pay - increase - fringe benefits - welfare fund. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Stroudsburg Fur Dressing Corporation vs. Fur Dressers Union, Local 2F and Fur Floor Workers Union, Local 3F, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  11/26/74. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Correspondence, briefs.
- Sucrest Corporation vs. ILA, Local 9, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  11/11/77. Issue: Rates of pay - differentials in pay. Issue: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Sucrest Corporation vs. ILA, Local 9, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  4/5/76. Issue: Shift scheduling. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation.
- Suffolk County Water Authority vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 393, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  12/29/77. Issue: Suspension - assignment of job - weather conditions - overtime. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Sunshine Biscuits, Inc. vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers, Local 50, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  9/30/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Sunset Nursing Home, Inc. vs. Joint Board, Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Florida Division, Local 1115, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  7/17/79. Issue: Subcontracting - layoff. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Sunweave Linen Corporation vs. UAW, District 65, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  5/20/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - improper job attitude - general attitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits, supporting documentation.
- Swiss Air Transport Company vs. IAM, Lodge 100, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  4/21/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty. Includes: Award only.
- Swiss Air Transport Company vs. IAM, Lodge 100, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  3/21/73. Issue: Suspension. Includes: Award only.
- Tarrytown Hilton vs. Hotel, Restaurant, and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  2/12/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination - leaving work area without permission. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Tavern-on-the-Green vs. Hotel, Restaurant, and Club Employees, Local 6, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  5/19/82. Issue: Rates of pay - increase. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Teachers College of Columbia University vs. UAW, District 65, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  2/8/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - unsatisfactory work. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Telescu Fuel Company vs. IBT, Local 191, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  7/20/81. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, briefs, correspondence, exhibits. No Award.
- Tickle (Arthur) Engineering Works vs. ILA, Local 1277-1, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  10/31/77. Issue: Fights and altercations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Trane Company vs. IAM, Lodge 1296, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  12/2/70. Issue: Discipline - discharge - Strikes - work stoppage. Includes: Award only.
- TRW, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 239, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  11/3/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Traffic Club of New York vs. Hotel, Restaurant and Club Employees, Local 6, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  9/30/80. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation
- Trans-Tel Corporation vs. IBEW, Local 1212, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  2/9/70. Issue: Discipline - discharge - incompetence. Includes: Award only.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Beverly Simmons, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  3/29/82. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - tardiness. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation. No Award.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Steve McCannon, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  3/28/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Yvonne Beavers, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  9/21/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, Local 551, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  4/4/77. Issue: Rates of pay. Includes: Correspondence, briefs, Arbitrator's notes, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, Local 551, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  4/4/77. Issue: Vacation - accrual. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation.
- Trans-World Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, Local 551, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  11/16/76. Issue: Scheduling - job assignment. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, Local 551, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  1/12/76. Issue: Suspension - absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Stanford Robinson, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  10/3/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge - misconduct - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, supporting documentation, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Marysia Wojcik, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  7/9/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Anna-Lisa Singer, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  1/12/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - absences - unauthorized. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Joseph Jerro, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  2/10/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - dishonesty. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs.
- Trans-World Airlines vs. IAM, Lodge 142, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  5/4/76. Issue: Demotion. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.
- Trans-World Airlines System Board of Adjustment vs. Pauline M. Ralph, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  4/21/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge - alcoholism. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, briefs, exhibits.